{
    "id": "e512f35e18fe40ab95c2573088a7a21f",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They sold the horse because it …………….. old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him what his name ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He finished first though he …………………. late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "began",
                "was begun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Whenever we ………………….. we talk of our college days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were meeting",
                "meet",
                "met"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He told them that they ………………….. wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He would succeed if he ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tries",
                "tried",
                "was trying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was so tired that he ..................... barely stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "could have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Newton discovered that the force of gravitation ....................... apples fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "made",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard that he …………………. win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When the sun set, we ………………… home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}